[Mindy] I love these.
[Emily] I guess.
What kind of flowers say,
"Hey! Welcome back to the office.
Sorry I betrayed you"?
It's only been two weeks
since she had that baby.
What kind of flowers say,
"Go back to bed, hon"?
I know, right?
But since the McDisaster,
I've had to work double time
to prove to Madeline that I'm loyal
or I could end up fired at two places.
Oh, my God, then where would I live?
How's Alfie?
I don't know.
He barely responds to my texts.
I just want to jump on the train
to London and tell him how I feel.
But I'm single-handedly
holding down the fort at Savoir.
Well, Madeline is lucky to have you.
Forget flowers.
Just get her a little bouquet
of Emily Coopers.
Except most of our French clients
are jumping ship to Sylvie's firm.
Ugh! Madeline has no idea
how bad things are.
- But she will soon.
- [chuckles]
This is going to be the longest day.
Actually, the day after tomorrow
is the longest day.
It's solstice.
Oh, well, thanks for the pagan
calendar update.
It's a thing in Paris.
The whole city celebrates.
It's my favorite.
Called Fête de la Musique.
The band and I will play in the third.
Mindy, you should be playing
at the jazz club,
not busking on the streets of Paris.
Does Benoît know you turned them down?
No, no, I don't want to break up the band.
And I didn't want to work
in two places at once.
I saw how that went for you.
Oh, glad I could be your cautionary tale.
Honestly, same.
Bonjour!
She's back!
Oh! Everybody's here now! It's a party!
Emily, this is Josette, the au pair.
Enchantée, Josette.
[Madeline] And you know Jack.
[Emily] Yes! Hello there, Jack!
We met once in the hospital.
You were very popular.
Because he's the biggest baby
they delivered in months!
They kept calling him le grand baby.
I thought that's why they kept me there
for three extra days.
To do "perineal re-education."
The more pressing matter
is that Chicago doesn't understand
why Sylvie and the entire
French office walked out.
I left out the part
where you followed them.
I appreciate that.
And I hope you know that I'm here for you.
I knew re-staffing would be a priority.
So I called a couple
of French recruiting firms.
Chasseurs de tête, as it were,
and I have a stack of resumes.
Well, our only real concern
is replacing one person.
Sylvie.
That's all that matters to Chicago.
They're working on it.
[in French] Rimowa, Pierre Cadault,
Maison Lavaux, Zimmer hotel, and you.
Our calling card.
It's so beautiful.
So potential clients get a sense
of the talent they are surrounded by
when they sign with Agence Grateau.
Make sure Sandrine at Tiffany gets one
before our meeting this afternoon.
We should post
a picture of the box to our social.
One small problem. We don't have a social.
Your dress for
Pierre's Museum retrospective.
Direct from his atelier.
My very own Cadault.
They asked that you not
eat or drink anything while wearing it.
And they'll need it back. Dry cleaned.
We should also make sure Sandrine
gets an invitation to Pierre's show.
It's important everyone knows
he's our client.
[cell phone chimes]
Let's go. I don't want to be late
for a meeting at Tiffany.
Oh, uh, Sylvie set that meeting last month
before she left.
Well, the meeting's with Savoir,
not Sylvie, so we're going.
Come on!
Oh. [groans]
Bonjour.
Merci.
Check out those two business mavens.
I hope they're not our competition.
They look pretty fierce.
[both chuckle]
[Emily clears throat]
Bonjour, Sandrine.
Je suis Madeline Wheeler from Savoir.
Bonjour.
I had a meeting
with Sylvie Grateau at this time.
No, no. You're meeting was with Savoir.
Sylvie no longer works for us.
I'm Madeline Wheeler.
And this is my associate...
Emily?
[in French] Oh, this isn't possible.
[in English] No, not again.
My apologies, Sandrine.
This woman has the nasty habit
of showing up at my meetings.
Your meeting is for Savoir.
We are Savoir.
[in French] Not you.
[Sylvie in English] That's the confusion.
We are Agence Grateau now.
It's my new company.
I believe you've seen Sylvie's box.
Rimowa, Pierre Cadault?
Zimmer et Maison Lavaux.
[chuckles]
Excusez-moi, madame,
I'm not sure if you realize
but when Gilbert Group acquired Savoir,
you all signed a strict non-compete.
Okay, I'll let you two fight this out.
Sandrine.
Read your contract, Syl.
Or better yet, have your lawyer do it.
Come on, Emily.
I can't believe you called her "Syl."
Emily, get your head in the game.
At the very least, Maison Lavaux
should be working with us.
You had a relationship with Antoine.
Not like Sylvie did.
I should hope not, but we need
to make it very clear to Antoine.
He cannot work with Sylvie
without legal repercussions.
I have a long-standing
relationship with Sylvie.
I'm a creature of habit,
what can I say?
And I am a creature
of enforceable contracts.
Sylvie may have left Savoir,
but she cannot take our accounts.
What is she talking about?
She signed a non-compete.
With the Gilbert Group,
whose lawyers
do not take these matters lightly.
Then have them call my lawyers.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a meeting with my new CFO.
Alfie?
[Alfie] Hello, Emily.
Wait, you're the new CFO?
You're supposed to be in London.
Well, Antoine offered me a job.
I was going to tell you,
but it's just been so busy.
You've been in Paris this whole time
without telling me?
Okay. Why don't you two lovebirds sidebar
this conversation for your own time?
- Let's go.
- You'll be hearing from our lawyers.
So you're suing me for not calling you?
Emily, I just need to know.
Are you on my team or not?
Yes, of course I am.
Then how did you not know
your own boyfriend's here in Paris
working with Antoine?
Because, I guess, he's not my boyfriend.
[sighs]
Emily, I am sorry,
but you are getting played.
We both are.
Try not to disappoint me a third time?
- Bonjour.
- [in French] Glass of white wine, please.
- Of course.
[in English] It's not nice to drink alone.
Hi!
- Can I join?
- Yeah, of course.
And it's not nice to eat alone either,
which is what I do most nights
waiting for Gabriel.
- The life of the chef's girlfriend.
- [Gabriel] Hey.
Salut, mon amour.
Emily, this is a surprise.
Hi.
So I have some interesting news.
Alfie is in Paris working for Antoine.
I think I'm wanted in the kitchen.
Wait, you knew?
We both did.
Did he finally call you?
No!
I walked into Antoine's
and they introduced me to his new CFO.
He asked us not to say anything.
He wanted to tell you himself.
But you guys are my friends.
I wish he didn't put us in the middle.
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
You've kept things from me before,
didn't you?
Sorry, I should have told you about Alfie.
Look, I really
want to be friends, Camille.
And that means
we have to trust each other.
I want that, too.
I really do.
Hey, Cooper.
I'll let you two talk.
So I guess everyone knows
you stayed in Paris except for me.
What's going on?
How did you end up working with Antoine?
I got to spend a lot of time with him
at my going-away party that you missed.
I had a few ideas about Maison Lavaux
and I guess he really liked them.
- This all happened at the party?
- No, not all.
You see, once I got to London,
Antoine asked if I could come back.
He wanted to hear more.
So I did.
And by the end of this amazing lunch,
he asked me to be his CFO.
I mean, it all happened pretty fast.
So why keep it all from me?
I was picking up the hints
that you and I weren't on the same page.
I didn't want you to think
I was coming back to Paris for you.
No, I'm really sorry you felt that way.
I didn't make this up.
I put myself out there,
and you left me hanging.
I... I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
It's been really nice to see you, Cooper.
Dinner's on Antoine.
[door opening]
Oh, my God,
Alfie's been here the whole time.
How did you know?
We basically live in a dorm.
I ran into Camille crossing the quad
and I heard you two were
having drinks in the commons.
[laughs]
- But seriously, are you okay?
- No.
I'm just confused.
I'm kind of mad, but he looked so good.
- Suit?
- Suit.
Spread collar shirt.
I wanted to poke my finger
above his tie knot and pull it down.
Hot.
He said he felt like he put himself
out there and I didn't reciprocate.
- Well, you didn't.
- Well, I was wrong.
And now he's really hurt
and he's completely closed off.
And he's working for Antoine!
- That's...
- How crazy is that?
[singing] ♪ What's it all about, Alfie? ♪
Huh?
The Dionne Warwick song?
"Alfie"? Come on!
♪ What's it all about
When you sort it out, Alfie? ♪
Okay, I got it. I get it, I get it.
I deserve this.
I didn't realize what I had
until I lost it.
No, no, he's hurt,
but that doesn't mean you lost him.
Really?
Yeah, but you have to really put yourself
out there if you want him back.
Yeah, well, the American dream
turned into the French nightmare.
Best to you as well.
[in French] You're gonna make some other
marketing firm really happy one day.
Voilà. Au revoir. Au revoir.
This is so hard.
Madeline sent emails
to all of our clients,
they want to know what's happening.
All our business is kaput.
No, we still have Pierre Cadault.
And the non-compete clause is only valid
for one year, it's not forever.
So we have no clients.
We'll find new ones, Julien.
You didn't think starting a business
was going to be easy, did you?
No.
[in English] Hey, Madeline,
can I get your approval on...
- Bonjour!
- Oh, you're pumping!
Yeah. Jack's on a nursing strike.
So French.
[chuckles]
Anyway, I'm happy to report
that the non-compete went out.
I bet Sylvie shit her pants.
Is this the best course of action?
It's not necessarily
driving business our way.
Yes, but it's keeping it
out of Sylvie's hands
while we find ourselves
a French president.
You know what someone said to me recently
when I was in a tough spot?
Push. Even when it hurts.
- Hey!
- Hi!
- Luc!
- Emily!
I've missed you.
I missed you, too.
If Madeline hadn't come back out here,
we'd still be working together.
- True, but Sylvie's ego is also to blame.
- Mmm.
I know she's hurting,
but we built up so many relationships
over the years just to lose them.
I feel terrible.
We are all suffering.
I am usually like a big cock.
What?
You know, proud, tall,
protector of the flock.
A rooster.
Yes! The rooster.
The cock, or the rooster,
is a symbol in France.
Able to sing
even when their feet are in the shit.
That is me.
But right now...
even I cannot sing.
Then I think we need
to do something about it.
I am going to walk the labyrinth
at the Jardin des Plantes.
Would you like to join me?
Actually, we're interviewing
for a new president of Savoir
and I have just the person for the job,
but I'm going to need your help.
Why didn't I think of this before?
Luc, you're the perfect candidate!
You've got the experience,
you know the brands, you know luxury.
No, no. No, no, no. It's not me.
There's only one person
who is right for this role.
And that is...
Sylvie.
I'm sorry. What?
Sylvie has all the relationships.
Pierre, Lavaux, Zimmer, Rimowa.
All those clients want to work with her.
Not with me.
She's what Chicago
bought in the first place.
The only one
who can replace Sylvie is Sylvie.
Okay. This is an ambush.
We are hurting. You're hurting.
Sylvie's pride is damaged.
You made your point.
And now you need to apologize
and to beg her to come back.
Why don't I just stab myself in the eye?
And the French love flattery.
You have to talk to French people
in a certain way.
They like to hear sweet things.
"Bonjour, bonsoir, après vous, merci."
Remember. French is
the language of diplomacy.
[sighs]
And you have an opportunity here
to be a diplomat.
Ambassador Madeline Wheeler, anyone?
- Yeah?
- [chuckles] That's stupid.
Plus, Sylvie won't want to meet me.
I know where she'll be tonight.
And you can be there, too.
Come to Pierre Cadault's retrospective
at costume museum. Both of you.
This is the perfect place for you
and Sylvie to bump into each other.
What a bonne idée.
Not such a bonne idée in my book.
I may be running out of options.
[groans]
Any tips on where I can
find a dress last minute?
Bien sûr.
So cool!
Ne touchez pas, madame!
[chuckles]
Sorry, I can't help myself.
No, no, no.
I should not be touche-ing the couture.
This was a very special collection.
Put Pierre back on the map
for a lot of people, so I totally get it.
Nicolas de Leon.
Yes, I know, of course.
I know everything about you.
Your father runs JVMA,
home to almost every important
luxury brand.
He has three sons, all in the business.
You are the youngest, but you're
supposed to be most like your dad,
all the way down
to his love of racing cars.
Emily Cooper, Savoir.
Savoir!
You are all behind Ringard,
the collection
that's reinvented Pierre Cadault.
- [chuckles]
- I know a few things, too.
Well, then you know
how successful we can be.
I would love to meet you for lunch or
a drink to discuss your marketing needs.
If you've really done your homework,
you would know that we do our marketing
for all of our brands in-house,
- but I hope we can still have that drink.
- Of course.
Excuse me.
I just saw a friend of mine walk in.
What are you doing here?
I'm just stealing your shine,
as per usual.
Take it. I have too much.
My plus one arrived.
Where's my other plus one?
Um...
Pumping.
It's such a struggle
not working with you guys.
Hopefully, after tonight,
everything will be fixed.
Madeline is going to ask Sylvie
to come back to Savoir!
I... I don't think it's that shocking.
It's a couture car crash.
Oh, merde!
[exhales]
Bonsoir, Sylvie.
[chuckles]
Well, you definitely wore it better.
Really, Madeline?
First Savoir, now this?
Are you actually trying to be me?
[laughs]
Wow, Sylvie.
Where did you get that?
At Louez le Runway.
It's a rental?
That's disgusting.
No, they have
a very rigorous cleaning process.
[clears throat]
Look, uh...
Sylvie.
I may be able to put on the dress,
but you...
have a way with clients and culture...
I can't even begin to emulate.
I took for granted
what you bring to the company and...
I am...
I'm sorry.
But let's be honest. We're both suffering.
I don't want to beg, but, well, here I am.
We would love to have you back
as president of Savoir.
Wait. Let me understand.
First you try to destroy my company,
then you want me to work for you?
With me.
And with a substantial
pay package increase,
including taking off
the entire month of August,
something we in America
only can dream about.
[chuckles]
Oh. [chuckles]
What a tempting offer.
[chuckles]
Will I still have the pleasure
of reporting to the board in Chicago?
Well, the pleasure would be theirs.
Perhaps I could visit
corporate headquarters?
How about a Cubs game
and a tour of the Loop?
Let's not forget the deep dish pizza.
Until it's coming out of your ears.
[both laugh]
Oh, God, you make it sound so enticing.
But...
me and an American company,
it's like you in that dress.
It just doesn't fit.
[Madeline clears throat]
Sylvie, come on.
You're down to one client.
Yeah.
I may only have Pierre
but one marquee client is enough.
[Pierre] May I have
your attention everyone, please?
[in French] Thank you
to the Decorative Arts Museum
for this wonderful tribute.
So many beautiful memories here.
I've been blessed with a long career.
And I look forward
to it getting even bigger.
[in English] And that is why
I'm thrilled to announce
that JVMA will be
acquiring Pierre Cadault.
[crowd applauding]
- Did you know about this?
- No.
This is a shock.
Even worse than the dresses.
JVMA doesn't work
with outside marketing firms,
which means that Pierre
is going to drop Sylvie.
Well, well, well.
Seems like you're now
down to zero clients.
And my offer just expired.
And for the record,
I think I wore it better.
[sighs]
[in French] I really wish you'd
talked to us
before turning down Madeline's offer.
- Are you joking?
- Oh, no.
We sacrificed a lot to work with you.
Julien.
[in English] Pierre, over here!
Give us a smile.
[in French] I have to say, I feel a little
blindsided, Pierre.
Until the deal was final,
I had to keep it secret.
I promise we'll talk tomorrow.
But tonight is about Cadault, not Grateau.
[chuckles]
[in English] Smile, darling.
Smile, my dear.
Sylvie, thank you for meeting me.
Well, congratulations on your acquisition.
Not sure why we're meeting.
I know you do all your marketing in-house.
Yes, we do.
But I love the work
Savoir has done with Pierre...
I'd like to bring you on board
to work for the Cadault line exclusively.
Well.
I have a firm now
and staff to think about.
We expect you to bring your own staff.
As much as I love Pierre, I've never
worked with only one client.
As I understand it, right now,
you don't have any clients.
I believe I'm throwing you a lifeline.
Well, thank you for your generous offer.
Let me think about it
and I'll get back to you.
You have until the end of the day.
It's the longest day of the year.
Should give you enough time.
[in French] So what happens
to Agence Grateau?
It dissolves.
We would be employees of JVMA.
I know you made a sacrifice
to come with me
and so I wanted to discuss this with you.
It's a good offer.
It's a huge company.
I'm sure there are amazing benefits.
You'll have your holidays.
You won't have to worry,
everything will be taken care of.
We'll all be secure.
What do you think, Luc?
I say stick to your guns, Sylvie.
We can do this.
You didn't think starting a business
would be easy, did you?
Are you sure?
Yes!
[sighs in relief]
Thank you.
Let's go enjoy the Fête de la Musique.
[Sylvie chuckles]
[Luc laughs]
[music playing]
[Mindy singing] ♪ Smile
For your heart is aching ♪
You know, I'll give it to Paris.
Even when you're having a bad day,
the city is looking great.
It's feeling good, it's having fun,
and it kind of rubs off on you, you know?
Solstice is a very important time
of the year.
It brings so much opportunity.
Yeah. It's like the sun saying,
"Okay, let's try this again."
[Alfie] Gabriel!
- Alfie!
- Hey.
- Good you could make it.
- How's it going?
- Hi.
- Hey.
So...
I was thinking and you were right.
I wasn't giving you all you deserve.
And after you left,
all I could think about
was how much I miss you
and how much I messed up.
Look, if you don't mind, Cooper,
I've had a really long day,
and I'd rather not talk about
our relationship history right now.
Let's just enjoy the music.
[singing] ♪ That's the time
You must keep on trying ♪
♪ Smile, what's the use of crying? ♪
♪ You'll find that life
Is still worthwhile ♪
♪ If you just smile ♪
[crowd cheering]
Merci à tous.
Thank you so much.
You can find us most nights
and weekends on the Pont des Arts Bridge...
Well, actually,
you can find as two at Pont des Arts,
but you can find Mindy
at La Trompette Bleue
where she'll be performing
three nights a week.
[crowd cheering]
What is going on?
You wouldn't answer
the club owner's calls,
so he called Benoît
and he accepted the offer for you.
- I don't want to give this up.
- Hey, you have to.
You should be playing in that club.
We'll be your biggest fans.
Well, I'll be your fan.
He can be a groupie.
Is that okay?
- I'm so happy for you!
- Hi.
Um...
Can I borrow this?
What are you doing?
Putting myself out there.
[laughs]
- I... [clears throat]
- [feedback buzzes]
♪ What's it all about... ♪
♪ Alfie? ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ Is it just for the moment we live? ♪
♪ What's it all about ♪
♪ When you sort it out, Alfie? ♪
♪ Are we meant to take
More than we give? ♪
♪ Or are we meant to be kind? ♪
- [playing chords]
- [chuckles]
♪ I believe in love, Alfie... ♪
Cooper, what have I got to do
to get you to stop singing?
♪ Without true love we just exist, Alfie ♪
♪ Until you find the love you've missed ♪
- ♪ You're nothing, Alfie ♪
- ♪ Alfie ♪
[crowd cheering]
[Mindy] Yeah!
You're crazy, Cooper.
You know that.
[laughs]
[crowd cheers]